<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anas Boukharta</title>
    <description>my rants, sometimes to take seriously, sometimes not!</description>
    <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://hypefi.github.io//blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 11:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 11:50:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.2</generator>

    
      <item>
        <title>On Avoiding Anger</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/12/09/on-avoiding-anger/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/12/09/on-avoiding-anger/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Avoiding entertainment as a mean to find the way</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Enchantment is the means through which
• we may gain access to sacredness.
Entertainment is the means through which we distance ourselves from it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly, when you are in a tiktok frenzy or ann instagram non stop watch or any other social media, you are in a reactionary state that is not meditative or leaving space for the sacred to enter the heart and clean the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eyes are the source, the main source of information that enters the heart, when you keep giving it virtual input all day long, your heart is confused and cannot see the truth. Like mud you cannot see through it. And the only way is to settle so that the mud settles at the bottom and the waters become clear. Of course this is an old problem, which all major religions and especially mystics have delved into, but the advice is even more important now, in the age of constant distraction and entertainment. Imagine buddhists were giving the advice of settling and meditating 2500 years ago and to avoid distractions in a world who was clearly devoid of many distractions that we see today. What would they say today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;many of the problems that seem impossible to solve are not solved because no one can see through the mud, and simply everybody needs to sit calmly for a long time until it clears and people starts to understand the position of each others persons, and see through the heart of the situation. This will help solve many problems that seems paradoxical, and impossible to solve like climate change, the nuclear proliferation, AI, and so on… Challenges that are so big that the haste cannot solve them, only stillness can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God cannot be found in noise and agitation. His true power and love are revealed in what is hardly perceptible, in the gentle breeze that requires stillness and quiet to detect.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/12/05/Avoiding-entertainment-as-a-mean-to-find-the-way/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/12/05/Avoiding-entertainment-as-a-mean-to-find-the-way/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The insiduous impact of screens</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We may think that screens have been around for more than half a century and that now their impact is well documented and so on… But I think that although we see this change as a necessary change of technology that has brought post modern society to fruition, we fail to realize the impact of them on our psyche. (I mean we common people although we know that they may not be that bad we don’t take serious measures against them, like cigarettes in the 60’s)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my humble observations the screens can have an impact that is so bad that is it is deadly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me explain, the disassociation from real life that the screens bring is of an impact that is more severe than what we think, many people fail thus to take care of many aspects of their lives, real relationships, work, family, conversations that solve problems through serious listening and giving advice from both sides…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This all has been lost with the distraction of screens and especially entertainment through screens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The famous book “Amusing Ourselves to Death” speaks about of all these impacts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You better read the book, I am not going to detail all the points but some quotes will guide your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All that has happened is that the public has adjusted to incoherence and been amused into indifference.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Enchantment is the means through which
• we may gain access to sacredness.
Entertainment is the means through which we distance ourselves from it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It is not necessary to conceal anything from a public insensible to contradiction and narcotized by technological diversions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Americans (and thus the whole connected world) no longer talk to each other, they entertain each other. They do not exchange ideas, they exchange images.
They do not argue with propositions; they argue with good looks, celebrities and commercials.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the deadly part is that it may lead to serious mental health problems that can lead to worse outcomes.
The least of it is that you don’t live your fulfilled life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The advice is : 
Get away from social media, news and entertainment in general and live your life. 
(Of course you can always use these platforms for work and sharing, but don’t stay in them for a long time they are eating your life and joy without you knowing it)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/12/04/The-insiduous-impact-of-screens-copy-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/12/04/The-insiduous-impact-of-screens-copy-2/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2 degrees and solutions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are following the climate news, well, let me be succinct. We are in big troubles, and I hate to say, I wish I could just live my life, surf in the beach, eat and sleep, and sometimes engage in intimate activities. But you know, this does not concern you, because you, you have AC; you live in a first-world country with access to the internet and so on. You are sheltered with the wealth you have amassed, and you feel powerful with all the gadgets and technology that surround you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently, the COVID crisis has not taught us anything about crises. When it hits, 1. Everybody is concerned suddenly, 2. Technology will not save us; it actually becomes a burden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, where are we heading as humanity? You and I are scared to lose our petty, job-related concerns that feed us for now by importing food from different countries. But what happens when multiple crop failures hit multiple regions, and the logistics are disturbed because people can’t feed themselves properly? Chaos. You heard that chaos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And let me tell you, you and I are not prepared for it at all. Chaos means violence, pain, and suffering. Oh no, but this can’t happen; we are civilized now, with laws, police, and the rule of law. “Civilization is three meals away from chaos” - Stalin. So, what are the solutions, you tell me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The solution is spiritual; it is not material. The spirit, the code running in the brain and the heart of people need to change; it needs to change drastically. The code in the heart is what makes possible what happens in the outside material world. Some hints:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is not having a big car, flying around the world to visit far-fetched countries for two weeks, having all sorts of material possessions, but being the most life-saving and flourishing helping being.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is not having more than your neighbor but being the most helpful and loving to your neighbor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is not “I am better than you,” but you and I are at peace.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is not developing new technology, whatever the consequences on life; it is developing only the technologies that help life flourish and using them wisely.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is seeing through eternity, and not life as an end in itself (difficult for most).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is sacrificing your needs for the needs of life to flourish (this will not diminish you but will bring into your heart gratitude, connection, and fulfillment that so many of us lack in our world).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Success is witnessing that our ancestors and religions had something important to say to us, and not believing that we had surpassed them in wisdom and intelligence because we have better tech (difficult for most technologists to see this).
These will help us align ourselves toward the new world; the crises we face are calls to change. I know you don’t want to hear this, neither do I. I wish I could just go eat, sleep, and engage in intimate activities like an animal until death comes upon me, and I am replaced by other human animals. But I do believe that we have higher purposes on earth, and if you believe the same, then you and I should change, we should do better, we should.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/11/21/2-degrees-end-times-and-solutions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2023/11/21/2-degrees-end-times-and-solutions/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consequences Of The Seemingly Inconsequential</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/08/23/Consequences-of-the-seemingly-inconsequential/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/08/23/Consequences-of-the-seemingly-inconsequential/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beware the invisible</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Beware the invisible, the invisible to the human eye, but still longering in behind the scenes. The invisible that you never suspect is here until it show up suddenly. The invisible that is flowing throughout the decor that you can’t see it with the eyes. The invisible that sometimes shows up in form of feelings, inspiration and thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The invisible that does not harm at slow doses, but is deadly through repetition and consistancy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The invisible that does not benefit in small intakes, but is very beneficial at long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not see pesticides, we do not see electromagnetic fields, we almost ddo not see the air pollution, the noise pollution, the light pollution, the stresses, the dis-eases, … until their toll is way beyond irreparibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are dangerous because the majority of people not only do not see their impact until it have done way too much damage, but usually they deny any impact because they cannot see it smell it ot taste it or feel it by senses, at first uncounter. And usually, fight all those who raise alarms. This story repeats itself and is an archetype across history. And maybe they will always people who listen and are precausious and people who aren’t. See Noah’s arch story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So they are in I don’t care state, which is fine if this invisible dangers does harm only themselves. The problem is that when these invisible harms are harming others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inflicting diseases to others because of carelessness in using these techonologies is very common, and way underapreciated in the field of medicine, where we are always trying to add more to the system ( the human body ) rather than substract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the main disease makers to the human body are pollutions as all of us know, yet we seem to neglect the constant stressors that are brang about from the industrial and modern lifestyle. Deeming it confortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where does the line between comfort and discomfort stops?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where does the constant search for comfort becomes a discomfort ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many seem to respond to these questions, by stating that life is not comfortable anyways, you will get sick and you will die anyway. That is true, but what type of sicknesses are we bringing upon ourselves that are unnecessary?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To not control basic inputs into our bodies have become too common, not controling the food intake, the air pollution, the electromagnetic smog. Is an infringement on the basic rights of the individual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tensions between what the individual can do and what society is providing has never been higher, as condensation and population is growing exponentially, there need to be a higher regard toward what the group can do or not.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/06/30/Beware-the-invisible/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/06/30/Beware-the-invisible/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New paradigms for the climate</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our ways of thinking about life are not in phase about the cosmos around us, the proof now is visible the ecosystems that sustain life on earth are dying and the very climate we live in is changing drastically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scientists are telling us we are in the verge of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dv8worldnews.com/rapport-alarmant-du-giec/article/2021/06/24/lhumanite-est-au-bord-du-cataclysme&quot;&gt;cataclism&lt;/a&gt;, and philosophers and thinkers have long been warning about the alienation of man from earth and his environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now the paradigm needs to shift our priorities are not in the right place that is why we see at last systemic impact on the climate and on all the organs and ecosystems of the earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earth sustains us in many ways that we even recognize or acknowledge, yet we are destroying it. It is a self-destruction act that is similar to one the addict person, who can’t keep from taking his drugs(fixes) even though he knows he is on the verge of calamity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the rare ways that make addicts wake up, are shocks, whether emotional or physical. These shocks create a break that is hard enough to awake the person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our case the last events that we have lived throughout 2020-2021, and that we may still live for some few years, are one of those. Painful for many, but welcome because they break the paradigms of thinking about life, about the routines, about what is possible and what is not, what can be done by humans and what is not. No one would have believed you in 2019 if you told them that cars, planes and mobility will be severely reduced in many countries in the world, you will be treated of an insane person if you ever said so, or at least you will laughed at. Yet, this is what is needed for climate, except it needs to be for the long run not a small period of time. To fail in doing so means, we are displacing the problem even further and risk even more severe consequences in the future (almost a la covid if no lockdown is done).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The objection from people is the economy, What people will do for work ? What about freedom of movement ? How are we going to feed people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is taken upside down, if nothing is done now and we do not restrict frivolous and unneeded movement, waste of energy, then, we risk into going into a world that even if we work hard we will not be able to feed people because the ecosystems will have collapsed and no amount of technology may help us. And even if so, life would be severely reduced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another argument is that we all going to die anyway, why not just enjoy the ride now, and to hell the next generations…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weirdly enough, this is the same argument that I get from people who smoke or drink. Why care about tomorrow, if I can be happy today?. The issue here is that you are not just being happy today, which is a philosophy I tend to agree with, but you are borrowing immensely from tomorrow, and that tomorrow is coming way sooner than you think with all its unintended consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By being unconsiderate, we are slowly killing a place in your heart that keeps life beautiful, the hopes, the joy, the beauty of doing a good act. We feel it, the heart feels it, and the earth too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is almost impossible to continue arguing here without going metaphysical, and without bringing up virtue and ethics. A person who does not care will not care. But individuals in society as whole needs to be informed of its acts and needs to be given clear choices about how to live their life and what impacts they have on earth and the future of society, and this by reforming first and doremost the economic systems ( By forbidding the interest &lt;a href=&quot;https://charleseisenstein.org/essays/we-cant-grow-ourselves-out-of-debt/&quot;&gt;debt based economy&lt;/a&gt; ), education systems (by reframing our values), the political ( by decentralization ), the agricutural ( by permaculture ), the technological ( by taking drastic measure against overconsumption such as restricting movement at night from motorized vehicules, retricting lights use in cities at night, by using technology only when its needed and not everywhere, anytime and anywhere).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caring for earth is caring for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/06/25/New-paradigms-for-climate/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/06/25/New-paradigms-for-climate/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We need more medical doctors that know about physics</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We need more medical practitioners that know about science and engineering, why? Because right now the machines and electrification are taking over the world, and we need to have doctors that understand the impact of technology on our bodies, environment, and ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of now, we don’t have a clear vision of what interacting with machines all day long is doing to our bodies, either short-term or long-term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do electromagnetic waves at different frequencies, and unknown to the biological body do to it? How does biology respond to the engineering around it? As far as I know, we live in the same universe as those machines we created, we live in the same time and space the electromagnetic waves are being used. What happens to our bodies when this type of pollution is omnipresent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know about pollution from fossil fuel cars is detrimental to health, why are we not asking the same question about electric cars, what do electric motors will do to our bodies during daily long drives…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To just dismiss these questions, is to not see that there is a problem in just trusting engineers who understand nothing about medicine and trusting doctors who know nothing about physics and engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need a new profession the general Practioner who understands physics and engineering, or the engineer who is trained in biology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We need people that understand both domains, and engineering products need to pass thorough testing on their health impact before hitting the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Engineers care only about if the products work they do not care about the impact on biology and the environment (while doing their work, they may think about it when they are daydreaming). They are not trained for it, and it is already very hard to make a product work, to add to it another layer of testing is inconceivable unless it becomes something natural to do, we build the device, and engineers biologists are included during the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doctors care about their patients (supposition, most of them not all) but if they don’t know how those devices interact with the bodies of their patients they can’t prescribe a “ stay away from your device “ routine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, it is maybe not a practitioner’s issue, it is a research issue. More research is needed on the subjects. 
While I agree on this point, I also think that both disciplines will benefit greatly from cross-pollination whether it is on research or in the training phase.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/06/17/engineers-doctors/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hypefi.github.io//blog/2021/06/17/engineers-doctors/</guid>
      </item>
    

    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
        
      
    
      
        
          <item>
            <title>About</title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;You love Minimalism, and you also love writing, Type is designed for you. Type focus on showing your content in a clean and simple way, focus on images, typography, and white space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the base Jekyll theme. You can find out more info about customizing your Jekyll theme, as well as basic Jekyll usage documentation at &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;jekyllrb.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, vix ut case porro facilisis, alia possit neglegentur vis te. Has cu eirmod abhorreant, vel civibus efficiantur cu. Eu summo elitr vix, iusto putant maluisset per ut, ne etiam vivendum adipisci vel. Vis omnis tempor accusam ei, justo perpetua liberavisse cu qui. Saperet aliquando adipiscing ius ne, ne facer euripidis est. Pro mundi nostrum suavitate et.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/about.html</link>
          </item>
        
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
        
          <item>
            <title>Style Guide</title>
            <description>At [Aspire Themes](http://aspirethemes.com/) I use a lot of tools to help me create WordPress, Ghost and Jekyll themes. Tools will range from development, design, services, hosting and automation.

Graphic design is the paradise of individuality, eccentricity, heresy, abnormality, hobbies, and humors. - George Santayana.

---

# Simple default styles for headings

## Simple default styles for headings

### Simple default styles for headings

#### Simple default styles for headings

##### Simple default styles for headings

###### Simple default styles for headings

---

* Ut at interdum nunc. Maecenas commodo turpis quis elementum gravida.
* Nunc ac sapien tellus. Quisque risus enim, tempus eget porttitor.
* Donec nibh massa, rutrum a sollicitudin eu, lacinia in lorem.

---

1. Ut at interdum nunc. Maecenas commodo turpis quis elementum gravida.
2. Nunc ac sapien tellus. Quisque risus enim, tempus eget porttitor in.
3. Donec nibh massa, rutrum a sollicitudin eu.

---

&gt; Graphic design is the paradise of individuality, eccentricity, heresy, abnormality, hobbies, and humors. - George Santayana

---

{% highlight js %}
'use strict';
var markdown = require('markdown').markdown;
function Editor(input, preview) {
  this.update = function() {
    preview.innerHTML = markdown.toHTML(input.value);
  };
  input.editor = this;
  this.update();
}
{% endhighlight %}

You can add inline code just like this, E.g. `.code { color: #fff; }`

{% highlight css %}
pre {
  background-color: #f4f4f4;
  max-width: 100%;
  overflow: auto;
}
{% endhighlight %}

---

Cras sed sodales enim. Duis nec erat magna. Sed scelerisque pretium mi et [unsplash](https://unsplash.com/) ullamcorper mauris aliquam ornare fringilla. In luctus commodo quam eget posuere.

---

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/97202679&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

---

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://embed.ted.com/talks/ted_halstead_a_climate_solution_where_all_sides_can_win&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

---

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;166&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/29738591&amp;amp;color=ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

---

&lt;p data-height=&quot;265&quot; data-theme-id=&quot;light&quot; data-slug-hash=&quot;YWvpRo&quot; data-default-tab=&quot;css,result&quot; data-user=&quot;kharrop&quot; data-embed-version=&quot;2&quot; data-pen-title=&quot;Referral Form&quot; class=&quot;codepen&quot;&gt;See the Pen &lt;a href=&quot;http://codepen.io/kharrop/pen/YWvpRo/&quot;&gt;Referral Form&lt;/a&gt; by Kelly Harrop (&lt;a href=&quot;http://codepen.io/kharrop&quot;&gt;@kharrop&lt;/a&gt;) on &lt;a href=&quot;http://codepen.io&quot;&gt;CodePen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script async src=&quot;https://production-assets.codepen.io/assets/embed/ei.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

---

![about](/images/pages/about.jpeg)

---

&lt;input type=&quot;text&quot; placeholder=&quot;I'm an input field!&quot;&gt;

---

&lt;button class='c-btn c-btn--small'&gt;Button&lt;/button&gt;

&lt;button class='c-btn'&gt;Button&lt;/button&gt;

&lt;button class='c-btn c-btn--full'&gt;Button&lt;/button&gt;

{% highlight html %}
&lt;button class='c-btn c-btn--small'&gt;Button&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button class='c-btn'&gt;Button&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button class='c-btn c-btn--full'&gt;Button&lt;/button&gt;
{% endhighlight %}
</description>
            <link>https://hypefi.github.io//blog/style-guide.html</link>
          </item>
        
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    
      
    

  </channel>
</rss>